Guide to the Ebenezer Warner Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Ebenezer Warner family papers
1775-1846
MS 1050
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
Deeds and other legal documents, chiefly relating to land in Hamden, Connecticut owned by Ebenezer Warner and his sons, Amos and Ebenezer. Sixteen of the transfers are to Eldad Wolcott of Hamden.
Warner, Ebenezer, 1733-1811
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased in 1948.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
This small collection is made up entirely of deeds and other legal documents, 1775-1846, pertaining to members of the Warner family living in and around Hamden, Connecticut. The deeds, sixteen of which are to Eldad Wolcott of Hamden, refer primarily to the land belonging to Ebenezer Warner (1733-1811), to his son Ebenezer (1767-1855), and to Amos Warner. Also among the papers are several writs, summonses, and subpoenas. The papers are arranged chronologically.
These documents were purchased for Yale University in 1948.
Families; Connecticut; Hamden (Conn.); Deeds; Warner, Amos; Warner, Ebenezer, 1767-1855; Wolcott, Eldad; Warner family
- Inventory
  - Deeds and legal papers
    - 1775, 1782-1784 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1785-1789 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1790-1793 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1794 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1795 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1796-1799 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1801-1802 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1803 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1804-1805 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1806-1809 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1811-1814 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1815-1817 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1818-1822 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1823-1829, 1846, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)